Guide to the Stanford University, Board of Trustees, Meeting Records SC1010
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Records created prior to 2010, 1885-2009; Series 1
  - Supporting material, 1905-1976, 1998-2009; Subseries 3; 28 Linear Feet (56 boxes)
    - Memo re endowment funds for Dormitory and Dining Hall buildings, Stanford Hospital building, and Water System; Real estate sales and leases, 1952 Oct 16 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Proposed expansion of Palo Alto Hospital, 1952 Nov 20 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Revaluation of Endowment Investment in Income Producing Institutional Property; 1940 Statement of Principles on Academic Freedom and Tenure; Graduate enrollment report; The Stanford Museum Proposed Plan; Audit Report, 1952 Dec 18 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Recommendations for appointments; Sterling's letters to Board on assorted issues; Hospital Governing Board, recommendations for establishing; Income Estimate 1955-56, 1955 Jan 20 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Contains only minutes of meeting from this unitdate which includes committee reports (66 page document), 1955 Jan 20 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Legal opinion on transferring San Francisco hospital facilities to the Presbyterian Group; Report of Gifts and Grants Received December 1959; Audit Reports for the University, Dept. of Athletics, Stanford Union, Stanford Press, 1960 Jan 21 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Report of Gifts and Grants Received January 1960, 1960 Feb 18 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Report of Gifts and Grants Received February 1960, 1960 Mar 17 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Report of Gifts and Grants Received March 1960, 1960 Apr 21 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Report of Gifts and Grants Received April 1960, 1960 May 19 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Report of Gifts and Grants Received April 1960, 1960 Jun 16 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Report of Gifts and Grants Received June 1960, 1960 Jul 21 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Report of Gifts and Grants Received September 1960; E.W. Littlefield's resignation from the Board of Trustees over a conflict of interest issue, 1960 Oct 20 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Report upon examination of Financial Statements for fiscal year ended Aug. 31, 1960, 1960 Nov 17 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Report upon examination of Financial Statements for fiscal year ended Aug. 31, 1960, 1960 Dec 15 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Report upon examination of Financial Statements for fiscal years ended Aug. 31, 1959 and 1960, 1961 Jan 19 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Letter of appointments to the Board to Lawrence Kimpton, Gardiner Symonds, S.D. Bechtel; Report of Gifts and Non-Goverment Grants Received & Summary of Government Grants Received, 1961 Mar 16 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Report upon examination of Financial Statements for fiscal year ended Aug. 31, 1961, 1962 Jan 18 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Report of Gifts and Non-Governernment Grants Received, 1962 Feb 15 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Letter requesting explanation of Trustees' stance on new liquor policy; Letter of appointment to Board to Benjamin Duniway; Report of Gifts and Non-Government Grants Received, 1962 May 17 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Small Group Housing Bonds of 1962, with Wells Fargo Bank, 1962 Oct 18 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Small Group Housing Bonds of 1962, with Wells Fargo Bank; Report of Gifts, Non-Government Grants, Government Grants, and Contracts Received, 1962 Nov 15 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Report of Gifts, Non-Government Grants, Government Grants, and Contracts Received; Stanford Trust Indenture for loans to private borrowers, 1963 Jan 17 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Indenture - Student Union Bonds of 1962, with Wells Fargo Bank, 1963 Jan 17 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Government bid for Student Union Bonds to be issued to finance Project No. CH-Calif-75(S); Report of Gifts, Non-Government Grants, Government Grants, and Contracts Received, 1963 Feb 21 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Letter of thanks to Morris Doyle, President of Board of Trustees by Herbert Hoover, 1963 Apr 18 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Letter of thanks for appointment to the Board from William Hewlett, 1963 Jul 18 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Housing System of Bonds 1963 - Series B, 1963 Sep 19 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Housing System of Bonds 1963, newspaper notice of sale; Report of Gifts, Non-Government Grants, Government Grants, and Contracts Received, 1963 Oct 17 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Resignation of Donald Russell from Board of Trustees, 1963 May 21 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Loan agreement for Housing Bonds of 1964 - Series C, 1963 Jul 16 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Letters of thanks for election to the Board from Roger Lewis and Fred Merrill, 1964 Oct (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Board resolution honoring Herbert Hoover, 1964 Nov 19 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Housing System of Bonds of 1964 - Series C, newspaper notice of sale, 1964 Dec 17 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Report of Gifts, Grants, and Contracts Received, 1965 Feb 18 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Letter of resignation from the Board, 1965 Jun 17 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Loan agreement for Undergraduate Men's Housing (Fraternity), 1965 Oct 21 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Report of Gifts, Grants, and Contracts Received, 1966 Mar 17 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Letter of thanks for appointment to the Board by W.L. Rogers, 1966 Apr 21 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Report of Gifts, Grants, and Contracts Received, 1967 Jan 19 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Report of Gifts, Grants, and Contracts Received, 1967 Feb 16 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Report of Gifts, Grants, and Contracts Received, 1967 Mar 16 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Report of Gifts, Grants, and Contracts Received; Departmental lists of the clinical (voluntary) faculty of the School of Medicine for 1967-68, 1967 Apr 20 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Letter of resignation from the Board by Emilie Cosgrove, 1967 May 18 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Detail of government grants received; Indenture, Small Group Housing Bonds of 1965, 1967 Sep 21 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Detail of contracts executed; Government bid, Small Group Housing Bonds of 1965, 1967 Oct 19 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Detail of contracts executed, 1967 Nov 16 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Detail of government grants received, 1967 Dec 21 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Background Data for a Discussion of Stanford University's Financial Needs for the Next Ten Years, 1968 Jan 18 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Resolutions honoring Al Manspeaker and the Faculty Advisory Committee on their selection of Kenneth Pitzer as President of Stanford, 1968 Sep 19 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Resignation letter of David Packard, 1969 Feb 19 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Minutes of special meeting to pass the resolution to construct Willow Road, 1969 Jul 22 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Resignations, 1969 Sep 17 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Letter from Edmund W. Littlefield, 1969 Oct 15 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Court petition to increase number of trustees from 23 to minimum of 25, with attached exhibits, 1969 Dec 19 (Box 32, Folder 2.1)
    - Final Report of the President's Ad Hoc Housing Advisory committee, 1970 Jun 12 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Trustee elections, 1970 Sep 15 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Appointment of Richard Lyman to presidency, 1970 Sep 24 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Resignation from Board of S. L. Washburn, 1970 Oct 13 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Resignation from Board of Gardiner Symonds, 1970 Nov 10 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence Henry Cabot Lodge, 1971 Jan 12 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Death of Gardiner Symonds, 1971 Jun 1 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - HUD document re student housing appartments, 1971 Oct 12 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - 1972 Mar 12 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Election of trustees, 1972 Jun 9 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Trustee position of Denis Hayes, 1972 Oct 10 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - [folder found empty 1/26/2009], 1974 Mar 12 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Resignation of Thomas V. Jones, 1974 May 14 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Trustee election, 1974 Jun 19 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Papers referred to in minutes; Statement to Board by Alliance for Radical Change; Clippings on Iran; Statement by ASSU Council of Presidents re faculty tenure issues; Clippings on tenure issues, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Papers referred to in minutes; Election of Alumni trustee, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - 1998 Feb
      Conditions Governing Access
      Restricted until Jan. 1, 2019.
      - Academic Policy Committee (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - Alumni/External Affairs and Development Committees (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - Audit and Finance Committees (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - Children's Services Physician-Hospital Integration Program (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - Development Committee (Box 33, Folder 5)
      - Land and Buildings Committee (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - Overseas Studies Report (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - Summary of Debt Transaction (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - 1998 Apr
      - Academic Policy Committee (Box 33, Folder 9)
      - Audit Committee (Box 33, Folder 10)
      - Development and Alumni/External Affairs Committees (Box 33, Folder 11)
      - Finance Committee (Box 33, Folder 12)
      - Land and Buildings Committee (Box 33, Folder 13)
      - Assorted documents: State of the Union Report on UCSF Stanford Health Care; and Planning Office document on current projects (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - 1998 Jun
      - Athletics (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - Budget Plan 1998/99 (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Development Committee (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - Finance Committee (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Housing (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - 1998 Oct
      - Academic Policy (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - Alumni/External Affairs (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - Audit Committee (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - Development Committee (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - Finance Committee (Box 34, Folder 10)
      - Housing (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - Land and Buildings Committee (Box 34, Folder 12)
      - SLAC Program and Prospects - report (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - 1998 Dec
      - Academic Policy (Box 34, Folder 14)
      - Alumni/External Affairs (Box 34, Folder 15)
      - Athletics (Box 34, Folder 16)
      - Audit Committee (Box 34, Folder 17)
      - Finance Committee (Box 34, Folder 18)
      - General business (Box 34, Folder 19)
      - Land and Buildings Committee (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - 1999 Feb
      Restricted until Jan. 1, 2020.
      - Academic Policy, Planning and Management (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - Alumni/External Affairs (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - Annual Report, 1998 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - Athletics (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - Audit Committee (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - Finance Committee (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - Land and Buildings Committee (1 of 2) (Box 35, Folder 7)
      - Land and Buildings Committee (2 of 2) (Box 35, Folder 8)
      - Assorted documents: Sand Hill Construction Program Overview; report of gifts; text of two addresses by Gerhard Casper (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - 1999 Apr
      - Audit Committee (Box 35, Folder 10)
      - Pres. Casper's statement on lands and housing (Box 35, Folder 11)
      - Finance Committee (Box 35, Folder 12)
      - Gifts Received 1998/99 (Box 35, Folder 13)
      - Medical Center, Committee on (Box 35, Folder 14)
      - Miscellaneous: establishment of professorship in experimental pathology; ballot for re-election of trustees Bass and Stein (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - 1999 Jun
      - Academic Policy Committee (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - Alumni/External Affairs Committee (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - Athletics, Ad Hoc Committee on (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - Audit Committee (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - Development Committee (includes "Stanford Stewardship Standards") (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - Finance Committee (includes Budget Plan 1999/2000 and "The Role of Endowment at Stanford") (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - Gifts Received, Report of (Box 36, Folder 7)
      - Miscellaneous: election ballot; Summary Of Proposed Review Procedures For Trustee Committee On Compensation (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - 1999 Dec
      - Academic Policy (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - Alumni/External Affairs (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - Athletics (Box 36, Folder 11)
      - Audit Committee (Box 36, Folder 12)
      - Finance (Box 36, Folder 13)
      - General Use Permit (Box 36, Folder 14)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 36, Folder 15)
      - Research Compliance Program (Box 36, Folder 16)
      - Revenue Policy Task Force (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - 2000 Feb
      Restricted until Jan. 1, 2021.
      - Athletics [clipping] (Box 36, Folder 18)
      - Finance Committee (includes "Report of the Revenue Policy Task Force" and "Stanford University Financial Policies") (Box 36, Folder 19)
      - Gifts Received, Report of (Box 36, Folder 20)
      - Land and Buildings Committee (re student health service building and 975 California Avenue research building) (Box 36, Folder 21)
      - Office of Technology Licensing, Annual Report 1998-99 (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - 2000 Apr
      - Academic Policy Planning (re faculty housing issues) (Box 37, Folder 1)
      - Alumni and External Affairs Committee (Box 37, Folder 2)
      - Audit Committee (Box 37, Folder 3)
      - Finance Committee (Box 37, Folder 4)
      - Gifts Received, Report of (Box 37, Folder 5)
      - Medical Center (Box 37, Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - 2000 Jun
      - Academic Policy Committee (Box 37, Folder 8)
      - Alumni and External Affairs Committee (Box 37, Folder 9)
      - Audit Committee (Box 37, Folder 10)
      - Development Committee (Box 37, Folder 11)
      - Finance Committee (includes Report of the Provost's Committee on Faculty Housing Policy, March 6, 2000) (Box 37, Folder 12)
      - Land and Buildings Committee (Box 37, Folder 13)
      - Medical Center (Box 37, Folder 14)
      - Miscellaneous (WASC Accreditation Team Report, May 2000; S. U. Budget Plan 2000/2001) (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - 2000 Oct
      - Academic Policy (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - Alumni and External Affairs Committee (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - Athletics (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - Audit Committee (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - Audit Committee (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - Development (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - Finance Committee (Box 38, Folder 7)
      - Land and Buildings Committee (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - 2000 Dec
      - Academic Policy (Box 38, Folder 9)
      - Audit Committee (Box 38, Folder 10)
      - Finance Committee (Box 38, Folder 11)
      - Gifts Received, Report of (Box 38, Folder 12)
      - Land and Buildings Committee (Box 38, Folder 13)
      - Medical Center, Committee on (Box 38, Folder 14)
      - Medicine, School of. Admissions CD-ROM (Box 38, Folder 15)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - 2002 Jun
      Restricted until Jan. 1, 2023.
      - Academic Policy (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - Alumni and External Affairs Committee (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - Athletics (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - Audit Committee (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - Finance (Box 39, Folder 5)
      - Lucile Packard Children's Hospital (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - Medicine, School of (Box 39, Folder 7)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 39, Folder 8)
      - Task Force on Minority Alumni Relations, 2002 Apr-Jun; Accession ARCH-2017-123 (Box 59)
    - 2002 Oct
      - Academic Policy (Box 39, Folder 9)
      - Alumni and External Affairs Committee [includes items re trails on Stanford lands] (Box 39, Folder 10)
      - Audit Committee (Box 39, Folder 11)
      - Special Joint Meeting, Committee on Audit and Compliance, Committee on Finance [binder] (Box 39, Folder 12)
      - Finance Committee (Box 39, Folder 13)
      - Jasper Ridge and Searsville Lake [includes "Maintaining Open Water at Searsville Lake. Final Project Report David and Lucile Packard Foundation Grant No. 98-5517"] (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - Land and Buildings (Box 40, Folder 2)
      - Medical Center Committee (Box 40, Folder 3)
      - Medicine, School of ["Translating Discoveries: a Strategic Plan for the Stanford University School of Medicine"] (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 40, Folder 5)
      - SCIR – Special Committee on Investment Responsibility (Box 40, Folder 6)
      - Undergraduate Education [CUE booklets on Overseas Studies, Bass Fellows, Undergraduate Research Programs, and Endowed Need-Based Scholarships; and Annual Report of the Vice Provost for Undergraduate Education 2001-2002] (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - 2002 Oct
      - Academic Policy, Planning and Management (Box 40, Folder 8)
      - Audit and Compliance (Box 40, Folder 9)
      - Development (Box 40, Folder 10)
      - Land and Buildings (Box 40, Folder 11)
      - Wallenberg Hall dedication (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - 2003 Feb
      Restricted until Jan. 1, 2024.
      - Academic Policy, Planning and Management (Box 40, Folder 13)
      - Audit and Compliance (Box 40, Folder 14)
      - Development (Box 40, Folder 15)
      - Finance (Box 40, Folder 16)
      - Medical Center (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - 2003 Apr
      - Academic Policy, Planning and Management (Box 41, Folder 1)
      - Audit and Compliance (Box 41, Folder 2)
      - Development (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - Finance (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - Medical Center (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - 2003 Jun
      - Athletics (Box 41, Folder 6)
      - Audit and Compliance (Box 41, Folder 7)
      - Campaign for Undergraduate Education (Box 41, Folder 8)
      - Election of Officer (Box 41, Folder 9)
      - Finance (Box 41, Folder 10)
      - Land and Buildings (Box 41, Folder 11)
      - Medical Center (Box 41, Folder 12)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 41, Folder 13)
      - Stanford Alumni Association (Box 41, Folder 14)
      - University Budget Plan (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - 2003 Oct
      - Academic Policy, Planning and Management (Box 41, Folder 16)
      - Assorted reports and publications (Diversity in Action; Reunion Homecoming Registration Guide; Annual Report of the Vice Provost for Undergraduate Education) (Box 41, Folder 17)
      - Audit and Compliance Committee (Box 41, Folder 18)
      - Finance Committee (Box 41, Folder 19)
      - Hennessy, "Accomplishments in 2002-3 Challenges for 2003-4" (Box 41, Folder 20)
      - Medical Center Committee (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 42, Folder 2)
      - Philosophy Talk – CD of pilot program by John Perry and Ken Taylor (Box 42, Folder 3)
      - Residential and Dining presentation (Box 42, Folder 4)
      - Stanford Alumni Association (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - 2003 Dec
      - Academic Policy, Planning and Management (Box 42, Folder 5)
      - Alumni and External Affairs (Box 42, Folder 6)
      - Audit and Compliance (Box 42, Folder 7)
      - Committee of the Whole (Box 42, Folder 8)
      - Development (Box 42, Folder 9)
      - Faculty (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - Finance (Box 42, Folder 11)
      - Land and Buildings (Box 42, Folder 12)
      - Medical Center (Box 42, Folder 13)
      - Trusteeship (Box 42, Folder 14)
      - Tuition Planning (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - 2004 Feb
      Restricted until Jan. 1, 2025.
      - Academic Policy, Planning and Management (Box 42, Folder 16)
      - Alumni and External Affairs (Box 42, Folder 17)
      - Athletics (Box 42, Folder 18)
      - Audit and Compliance (Box 42, Folder 19)
      - Awakuni, Gene, "Briefing on Student Life" (Box 42, Folder 20)
      - Bio-X Program (Box 42, Folder 21)
      - Budget Plan 2003/04 (Box 42, Folder 22)
      - Development (Box 42, Folder 23)
      - Finance (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - Focus Group on the Environment (Box 43, Folder 2)
      - Hennessy, "Accomplishments in 2002-3; Challenges Ahead" (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - Investment Responsibility (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - Land and Buildings (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - Medical Center (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - Public Affairs (Box 43, Folder 7)
      - Publications, miscellaneous (Box 43, Folder 8)
      - Miscellaneous materials [memo re Robert Proctor] (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - 2004 Jun
      - Academic Council, "Perspectives on Growth," a report of the Planning and Policy Board, June 10, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 10)
      - Academic Policy, Planning and Management (Box 43, Folder 11)
      - Alumni and External Affairs (Box 43, Folder 12)
      - Athletics (Box 43, Folder 13)
      - Audit and Compliance (Box 43, Folder 14)
      - Budget Plan 2004/05 (Box 43, Folder 15)
      - Finance (Box 43, Folder 16)
      - Land and Buildings (Box 43, Folder 17)
      - Medical Center (Box 44, Folder 1)
      - Miscellaneous [Commencement Week schedule] (Box 44, Folder 2)
      - Naming a School at Stanford University (Box 44, Folder 3)
      - Trusteeship (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - 2004 Oct
      - Academic Policy, Planning and Management (Box 44, Folder 5)
      - Accomplishments in 2003-4; Goals & Challenges fro 2004-5 [presentation by Hennessy] (Box 44, Folder 6)
      - Alumni and External Affairs (Box 44, Folder 7)
      - Athletics (Box 44, Folder 8)
      - Development Committee (Box 44, Folder 9)
      - Finance Committee (Box 44, Folder 10)
      - Land and Buildings Committee (Box 44, Folder 11)
      - Lucile Salter Packard Children's Hospital at Stanford, Affiliation Agreement (Box 44, Folder 12)
      - Medical Center Committee (Box 44, Folder 13)
      - Recent News Articles (Box 44, Folder 14)
      - Special Committee on Investment Responsibility (Box 44, Folder 15)
      - Stanford Management Company (Box 44, Folder 16)
      - Undergraduate Admissions (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - 2004 Dec
      - Academic Policy, Planning and Management (Box 44, Folder 18)
      - Alumni and External Affairs (Box 44, Folder 19)
      - Athletics (Box 44, Folder 20)
      - Audit and Compliance Committee (Box 44, Folder 21)
      - Committee of the Whole (Box 44, Folder 22)
      - Development Committee (Box 44, Folder 23)
      - Finance Committee (Box 44, Folder 24)
      - Hoover Institution (Box 44, Folder 25)
      - Land and Buildings Committee (Box 44, Folder 26)
      - Medical Center Committee (Box 44, Folder 27)
      - Miscellaneous (copy of letter from Gov. Schwarzenegger to Dianne Feinstein) (Box 44, Folder 28)
      - Stanford's Campaign for the New Century (draft of fund-raising statement) (Box 44, Folder 29)
    - 2005 Feb
      Restricted until Jan. 1, 2026.
      - Academic Policy, Planning and Management (Box 45, Folder 1)
      - Alumni and External Affairs (Box 45, Folder 2)
      - Annual Report [University], 2004 (Box 45, Folder 3)
      - Audit and Compliance Committee (Box 45, Folder 4)
      - Development Committee (Box 45, Folder 5)
      - Finance Committee (Box 45, Folder 6)
      - Governance Task Force (Box 45, Folder 7)
      - Hennessy, Accomplishments in 2003-4 Goals & Challenges for 2004-5 (Box 45, Folder 8)
      - Medical Center Committee (Box 45, Folder 9)
      - Miscellaneous [Haas Center, Hennessy's op-ed on Harvard president Lawrence Summer's comments] (Box 45, Folder 10)
      - Undergraduate housing, proposed changes (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - 2005 Apr
      - Alumni and External Affairs (Box 45, Folder 12)
      - Athletics (Box 45, Folder 13)
      - Audit and Compliance Committee (Box 45, Folder 14)
      - Development Committee (Box 45, Folder 15)
      - Finance Committee (Box 45, Folder 16)
      - The International Initiative (Box 45, Folder 17)
      - Miscellaneous (mailing re Special Patient Services; handout on Stanford Charter School Initiative) (Box 45, Folder 18)
      - Trustee election (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - 2005 Jun
      - Academic Policy, Planning and Management (Box 45, Folder 20)
      - Alumni and External Affairs (Box 45, Folder 21)
      - Audit and Compliance Committee (Box 45, Folder 22)
      - Budget Plan 2005/06 (Box 45, Folder 23)
      - Development Committee (Box 46, Folder 1)
      - Finance Committee (Box 46, Folder 2)
      - Land and Buildings Committee (Box 46, Folder 3)
      - Lucile Packard Children's Hospital (Box 46, Folder 4)
      - Medical Center Committee (Box 46, Folder 5)